<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<!-- ITC5202 - Your name : ..... -->
<portfolio>

   <author>Rafael Garcia</author>
   <date>4/17/2017</date>
   <time>13:17</time>

   <stock>
      <sName symbol="BA">Boeing Company</sName>
      <description>The Boeing Company engages in the design, development, manufacture, sale, and support 
                   of commercial jetliners, military aircraft, satellites, missile defense, 
                   human space flight, and launch systems and services worldwide. It also offers aviation 
                   services support, aircraft modifications, spares, training, maintenance documents, 
                   and technical advice to commercial and government customers. Its financing portfolio 
                   consists of equipment under operating leases, finance leases, notes and other 
                   receivables, assets held for sale or re-lease, and investments. The Boeing Company 
                   was founded in 1916 and is based in Chicago, Illinois.
      </description>
      <category>Industrials</category>
      <today open="125.68" high="125.72" low="124.81" current="125.68" vol="6274500" />
   </stock>

   <stock>
      <sName symbol="HPQ">Hewlett-Packard Company</sName>
      <description>Hewlett-Packard Company provides products, technologies, software, solutions, and 
                   services to individual consumers, small-and medium-sized businesses, and large 
                   enterprises, including customers in the government, health, and education sectors 
                   worldwide. Its Software segment offers enterprise information management solutions 
                   for structured and unstructured data, IT management software, and appliance 
                   deployment models. The company was founded in 1939 and is headquartered in 
                   Palo Alto, California.
      </description>
      <category>Industrials</category>
      <today open="23.78" high="25.15" low="23.78" current="23.78" vol="15922600" />
   </stock>

   <stock>
      <sName symbol="LUV">Southwest Airlines Corporation</sName>
      <description>Southwest Airlines Co. operates passenger airlines that provide scheduled air 
                   transportation services in the United States. It serves 97 destinations in 41 states, 
                   the District of Columbia, and the Commonwealth of Puerto Rico, as well as 6 
                   near-international countries. The company was founded in 1967 and is headquartered 
                   in Dallas, Texas.
      </description>
      <category>Transportation</category>
      <today open="17.21" high="17.94" low="16.77" current="17.73" vol="6554700" />
   </stock>

   <stock>
      <sName symbol="ED">Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc.</sName>
      <description>Consolidated Edison, Inc. engages in regulated electric, gas, and steam delivery 
                   businesses. The company provides electric services to approximately 3.3 million 
                   customers in New York City and Westchester County; gas to approximately 1.1 million 
                   customers in Manhattan, the Bronx and parts of Queens, and Westchester County; and 
                   steam to approximately 1,717 customers in parts of Manhattan. In addition, the company 
                   engages in the sale and related hedging of electricity to wholesale and retail customers.
                   Consolidated Edison, Inc. was founded in 1884 and is based in New York, New York.
      </description>
      <category>Utilities</category>
      <today open="59.15" high="59.89" low="59.03" current="59.89" vol="1298000" />
   </stock>

   <stock>
      <sName symbol="AA">Aluminum Company of America</sName>
      <description>Alcoa Inc. engages in the production and management of primary aluminum, 
                   fabricated aluminum, and alumina. Its products are used in aircraft, automobiles, 
                   commercial transportation, packaging, building and construction, oil and gas, 
                   defense, consumer electronics, and industrial applications. Alcoa Inc. was founded 
                   in 1888 and is based in New York, New York.
      </description>
      <category>Industrials</category>
      <today open="9.39" high="9.56" low="9.32" current="9.48" vol="16815260" />
   </stock>

   <stock>
      <sName symbol="AEP">American Electric Power Company, Incorporated</sName>
      <description>American Electric Power Company, Inc., a public utility holding company, engages 
                   in the generation, transmission, and distribution of electric power to retail 
                   customers. The company generates electricity using coal and lignite, natural gas, 
                   nuclear energy, and hydroelectric energy. It operates primarily in the states of 
                   Arkansas, Indiana, Kentucky, Louisiana, Michigan, Ohio, Oklahoma, Tennessee, 
                   Texas, Virginia, and West Virginia. American Electric Power Company, Inc. was founded 
                   in 1906 and is headquartered in Columbus, Ohio.
      </description>
      <category>Utilities</category>
      <today open="46.92" high="47.15" low="46.25" current="46.25" vol="20315100" />
   </stock>

   <stock>
      <sName symbol="CNI">Canadian National Railway Company</sName>
      <description>Canadian National Railway Company engages in rail and related transportation business 
                   in North America. It transports various goods, including petroleum and chemicals, 
                   grain and fertilizers, coal, metals and minerals, forest products, intermodal, and 
                   automotive products. The company operates a network of approximately 20,100 route miles 
                   of track that spans Canada and mid-America. The company was founded in 1922 and is 
                   headquartered in Montreal, Canada.
      </description>
      <category>Transportation</category>
      <today open="110.02" high="111.15" low="109.59" current="110.21" vol="573400" />
   </stock>

   <stock>
      <sName symbol="CVX">Chevron Corporation </sName>
      <description>Chevron Corporation engages in petroleum, chemicals, mining, power generation, and 
                   energy operations worldwide. The Upstream segment is involved in the exploration, 
                   development, and production of crude oil and natural gas. The Downstream segment engages 
                   in refining crude oil into petroleum products; marketing crude oil and refined products. 
                   The company is also involved in coal and molybdenum mining operations. The company was 
                   founded in 1879 and is headquartered in San Ramon, California.
      </description>
      <category>Industrials</category>
      <today open="120.81" high="121.57" low="120.68" current="121.21" vol="8235300" />
   </stock>

   <stock>
      <sName symbol="DAL">Delta Air Lines Inc.</sName>
      <description>Delta Air Lines, Inc. provides scheduled air transportation for passengers and cargo in 
                   the United States and internationally. The company sells its tickets through various 
                   distribution channels, including telephone reservations, and online travel agencies. 
                   Its also provides aircraft maintenance, repair, and overhaul services for other aviation 
                   and airline customers. The company was founded in 1924 and is headquartered in 
                   Atlanta, Georgia.
      </description>
      <category>Transportation</category>
      <today open="26.07" high="26.35" low="25.89" current="25.89" vol="10321500" />
   </stock>

   <stock>
      <sName symbol="MPC">Marathon Petroleum Corporation</sName>
      <description>Marathon Petroleum Corporation engages in refining, transporting, and marketing petroleum 
                   products primarily in the United States. The company owns and operates seven 
                   refineries in the Gulf Coast and Midwest regions of the United States. The company 
                   also transports crude oil and other feedstocks to its refineries and other locations.
                   The company is headquartered in Findlay, Ohio.
      </description>
      <category>Industrials</category>
      <today open="71.28" high="71.28" low="70.17" current="70.91" vol="2550200" />
   </stock>

   <stock>
      <sName symbol="PPL">PPL Resources Incorporated</sName>
      <description>PPL Corporation, an energy and utility holding company, engages in the generation, 
                   transmission, distribution, and sale of electricity to wholesale and retail customers 
                   in the United States and the United Kingdom. The company develops renewable energy 
                   projects; and provides energy-related products and services to commercial and 
                   industrial customers. PPL Corporation was founded in 1920 and is headquartered in 
                   Allentown, Pennsylvania.
      </description>
      <category>Utilities</category>
      <today open="31.28" high="31.28" low="30.17" current="30.91" vol="4655200" />
   </stock>

   <stock>
      <sName symbol="R">Ryder System, Incorporated</sName>
      <description>Ryder System, Inc. provides transportation and supply chain management solutions. 
                   It also offers fleet support services, such as fuel, insurance, safety, administration, 
                   environmental management, and information technology services. Ryder System, Inc. serves 
                   customers operating in various industries, such as automotive, food service, electronics, 
                   transportation, consumer packaged goods, grocery, lumber and wood products, and home 
                   furnishings. The company was founded in 1933 and is based in Miami, Florida.
      </description>
      <category>Transportation</category>
      <today open="66.73" high="66.81" low="65.44" current="65.89" vol="763900" />
   </stock>

   <stock>
      <sName symbol="T">ATT Corporation</sName>
      <description>ATT Inc. provides telecommunications services to consumers, businesses, and other
                  providers in the United States and internationally. The company operates in three 
                  segments: Wireless, Wireline, and Other. The Wireless segment offers various wireless 
                  voice and data communication services. The Wireline segment provides data services
                  and network integration. The Other segment provides application management, security 
                  services, and satellite video services. The company was founded in 1983 and is based 
                  in Dallas, Texas.
      </description>
      <category>Industrials</category>
      <today open="36.18" high="36.24" low="35.14" current="35.78" vol="19065800" />
   </stock>

   <stock>
      <sName symbol="UNP">Union Pacific Corporation</sName>
      <description>Union Pacific Corporation provides rail transportation services in North America. 
                   The company offers freight transportation services for agricultural products, 
                   food, and beverage products; and automotive products. It also provides transportation 
                   services for petrochemicals. In addition, the company offers freight transportation 
                   services for industrial products and construction products. Union Pacific Corporation 
                   was founded in 1862 and is headquartered in Omaha, Nebraska.
      </description>
      <category>Transportation</category>
      <today open="151.58" high="151.89" low="149.78" current="150.23" vol="1714000" />
   </stock>

   <stock>
      <sName symbol="WEC">Wisconsin Energy Corporation</sName>
      <description>Wisconsin Energy Corporation generates and distributes electric energy, as well as 
                  distributes natural gas. The company provides electric utility services to customers 
                  in the mining, paper, foundry, food products, and machinery production industries.
                  It also generates, distributes, and sells steam. The company was founded in 1981 and 
                  is headquartered in Milwaukee, Wisconsin.
      </description>
      <category>Utilities</category>
      <today open="42.81" high="43.14" low="42.81" current="42.93" vol="1252000" />
   </stock>

</portfolio>
